Gosh, what's this?
(Walking into a pocket of time in the heart of summer)
- My gosh. Look at the waterfall. - I see.
- This is the Waterfall Park. - Oh, my. What's this?
- That's a huge waterfall. - My gosh.
It's so big.
They did a great job with it.
- Gosh. - Seriously. Jungnang-gu...
is amazing.
My gosh. A trip is totally worth it.
(Today's spare time, Jungnang-gu)
- Gosh, it was a long wait. - Oh, my.
- Thank you for waiting. - Yes.
We found some spare time and came back.
- We're back. - Yes.
In the meantime, you won an award from SBS.
Right. They gave me an award for the first half of the year.
You won an award without me. What was the award?
I was on Whenever Possible.
I was also in the SBS drama.
- You were in that too. - Yes.
I was in "Phantom Lawyer."
We started filming the fifth season of Whenever Possible too.
They must've wanted me to work hard.
The award definitely is definitely giving off that vibe.
- It's like an attendance award. - No.
It's like a whip-cracking award.
- So I work... - So you work harder.
- Work harder? I see. - Yes. Work your tail off.
- It wasn't encouragement. - No, this is the vibe.
It was a mix of encouragement and a strong push.
- So don't be so disappointed. - I see.
- Okay. - Hey!
- Gosh. You startled me. - Wasp is here.
Jung Min.
- Hey! - Gosh. You startled me.
(Today's Whenever Friends: Hwang Jung Min and Jung Ho Yeon)
(Hey, brother.)
(He's our hope for a successful mission.)
(Actor Hwang Jung Min)
(She captivated the world with her steps on the runway.)
(She made a global debut as an actress in "Squid Game.")
(Top model and actress beloved by the world, Jung Ho Yeon)
(In the second half of the year,)
(she aims for the global audience with "Hope.")
(Zo In Sung is also in the movie.)
("'Hope' Finally Unfolds and Clearly Proves Why Cannes Raves About It")
("'Hope' Surpasses 4 Million Admissions")
("A Must-Watch Monster Movie in 2026 by BBC")
Jung Min.
- Gosh. - Why did you scream like that?
- Gosh, Wasp. Ho Yeon. - Amen!
I was right next to him, so my ear is about to burst.
My gosh, Wasp.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Ho Yeon. - Gosh, Jae Seok.
Aren't you hot?
It's super hot.
- My stylist... - Oh, my.
- keeps testing me. - She's wearing a leather jacket.
(It was really hot on the day of the shoot.)
I'm sweating profusely.
- Models are indeed different. - Gosh, no.
Fashionistas ought to wear leather jackets even if they sweat.
(Looking fashionable even in the heatwave)
- Sit down. - My face can't get red.
Gosh, that kid was smooth.
Right.
- Let's talk about "Hope." - Yes.
Your movie premieres tomorrow...
- as of the filming date. - Right.
But our episode will air on August 11.
- August 11? - I bet it'll still be in theaters.
- Right. - Yes.
There are people who still haven't watched our movie?
- Still? - Anyway,
are you done with your PR events?
No, we're just getting started.
- We'll make theater appearances. - You will?
- But... - You should visit many theaters.
- Right. - this is...
the number one TV program...
- from all three major TV stations. - Okay.
So this is our first PR appearance on a major TV show.
It's our first appearance on a TV show.
My mother called me...
and kept asking me if I wasn't promoting the movie.
I told her I was already promoting it.
She asked which show I was on.
So the elders can't keep up with our online PR appearances.
- You should be on TV. - Right.
They think...
you began promoting it when they see you on TV shows.
They can tell by TV shows.
- Right. - Yes.
By the way, when Wasp...
recently joined me...
on "Pinggyego" with Ho Yeon and In Sung, this is what he said.
He said he was super frustrated when he watched our show.
"How can they fail that?"
Right. He said he wanted to be on our show.
- Right. He said that. - Were you frustrated...
about the games when you watched our show?
No. I wasn't frustrated about the games.
There were so many original games.
- And they looked like fun. - But?
But I was frustrated that...
the guests couldn't handle the games well.
I was like, "Why can't they do that?"
- I see. You couldn't get it? - He kept criticizing them.
- Let me explain. - "My gosh. That little..."
Well, they're my juniors. You know?
- In Sung was on our show too. - Exactly.
- They're close friends of mine. - Yes.
I got super frustrated.
- The games looked winnable. - Right.
You should try it later.
I don't know what kind of game they prepared for today.
You should try it. Jung Min said he was confident.
I'm getting a feeling that he's going to be angry today.
- He can't control his temper. - No, listen.
- It's not that. - Okay.
I went to get my makeup.
- She said, "Don't get angry." - "Don't get angry."
I went to get my hair done. He said, "Don't get mad."
Everyone told me...
not to lose my temper or get mad.
(Beware of getting too invested in the games.)
Ho Yeon, do you exercise?
- I do Pilates. - Okay.
And I did some weight training.
But I took swimming lessons when I was a kid.
- You did? - So...
I'm confident when it comes to swimming.
But I don't feel so confident about ball sports.
But I'll stay focused today.
Yes. Try your best.
We should go and meet...
- Yes. - our Whenever Guest.
Let's head out to meet the first Whenever Guest...
- of our fifth season. Okay. - Yes.
Our first Whenever Guest is...
Jung Seo Woo.
"We work with pens during the day..."
- "and steel during the night." - What?
"Our biggest fear is losing muscles."
- They must work in fitness. - They must work in fitness.
"We always end our day by taking..."
"a post-workout picture."
"Our personality, appearance, and preferences are all different."
"But we bond over muscles."
"Jae Seok. Yeon Seok."
"How about doing some pull-ups with us today?"
(Pull-ups?)
- They either run a gym... - Right.
- or love working out. - Right. They...
All right. Shall we get going?
- Yes. - Let's go.
- Right? - We'll take public transportation.
Ta-da.
This neighborhood is really nice.
Jung Min.
- Have you been well? - Yes.
Did you and Yeon Seok work in a movie or drama?
- "Narco-Saints." - "Narco-Saints."
Right!
- Amen. - Amen.
- Amen. - You both played religious roles.
Yes.
- My pastor. - Oh, right.
- My preacher. - I always did this in the drama.
How come there's no second season of the drama?
It will be difficult for me to be in the second season.
- Right. - His character died.
- My character died. - Right, you can't be in it.
- I got arrested too. - You got arrested.
There should be a second season.
A lot of people mentioned that our movie should get a sequel...
- after watching it. - Yes.
If we think about the production budget...
- Right. - and the cast's schedules,
- Right. - there are...
so many things we must consider to make that happen.
- It won't be easy. - Right.
If there are people who want a sequel,
please invest in "Hope."
She's attracting investors on our show.
- She totally caught me off guard. - Gosh, Ho Yeon.
- Please invest in our movie. - Ho Yeon.
- The production company... - Ho Yeon, I didn't know...
- must be grateful. - you'd try to attract investors.
- As an actress in the movie, - You want a sequel too.
I'd love to keep working...
- with Jung Min. That's all. - I see.
- Isn't this the bus stop? - It's...
- This is the bus stop? - Gosh, look.
- Does Bus 2012 also go there? - Yes.
- Yes. - Bus 2012 also goes there.
- Why are you tagging your card? - No.
- I can pay for all of us. - We were going to pay.
- Really? - I...
- I can do it. - He already tagged in.
Let's sit here.
(They go all the way to the back.)
I got my own personal card because I was told to bring it.
- We'll play a lunch game later. - It's for lunch.
- I see. - That's for lunch.
Nice!
I love lunch games.
- Lunch games? Then... - Yes.
This feels surreal like I'm inside the TV...
- You are on TV. - because...
(A clear answer)
- You... - You're on TV.
Right.
Come on in.
- Come on in. - Come on in.
Have you been on TV shows from major TV stations?
- It's my first time appearing... - Any guest appearances?
as a guest like this.
So I'm not sure if I'm doing a good job.
I keep questioning myself.
Do you get competitive?
I'm super competitive.
Right now,
you feel like you need to do something.
But once we start playing games, that feeling will intensify tenfold.
My gosh. It will be a rush of dopamine.
Yes. Seriously.
"Why can't I succeed at this seemingly silly game?"
But was there ever a time you guys messed up on purpose...
for the entertainment of the show?
- Was there? - Gosh, never.
- We can't do that. - I think there was.
Hey, be honest.
- I bet there was a time like that. - Seriously. We can't fake anything.
- See it for yourself later. - We can't fake anything.
That never happens. You really want to succeed.
But sometimes, you just can't.
It's different when it's your turn. You try it.
- Here? - Thank you.
(Arriving at the destination)
My gosh, wait. Is it around here?
We have to cross the street and go up.
- Then they might be at a school. - Really?
I see.
- Let's cross here. - Okay.
I see. It's a school.
- It's a school? - Daewon High School.
Whenever we went to school,
- We never succeeded. - we never succeeded.
I see.
Your energy level seems to have gone down.
Should we cross here?
- My gosh. - It's a steep hill.
- But when you're on a hill, - Yes.
walking backward makes climbing the hill easier.
- Try it. - It's easier that way.
- You're right. - You're right.
Yes.
It's not that hard like this.
You're right.
(Out of breath)
Hey, there's another one.
(No matter how much they climb up...)
- Hey, this is... - Wait.
- This is a workout. - Is that the place?
- Oh, this is... - We must go up there.
Wasp, my gosh. This is...
If you're late to school, running up these hills...
Don't talk to me.
- Jung Min. - The stairs...
- Hold on. - Hey.
- Hey, this is... - Wait.
- It's a workout. - This is the place?
- I bet back in the day, - What?
gym teachers or the dean made students...
- do the duck walk here. - Right.
- If they're not properly dressed. - Right.
Or if they're late.
(Panting)
(She's struggling more than anyone.)
You're wearing the wrong outfit today.
It's summer.
- What do you call it? - My gosh.
- Students. - You know what?
- Since we came up high, the view... - What a great view.
I can see all the way to Gangnam.
My gosh. What an amazing view.
(The panoramic view of Seoul unfolds before them.)
The view is amazing.
That's the World Trade Center.
Right. I can see all the way to Samseong-dong.
- This is amazing. - Is that Namtaeryeong down there?
- This place... - Isn't it?
I can see Namtaeryeong in Seocho-gu.
That's that thing in Samseong-dong.
- That's the Star Tower. - Right.
There's the World Trade Center.
- I can see the Star Tower. - Yes.
- Oh, your building? - It's not mine.
- Why is that my building? - He's bragging about his building.
Come on, Wasp.
(Wasp is tackling Grasshopper.)
You know what? This is...
- We climbed up a lot. - the highest point we've been.
- Hold on. There's no elevator. - Oh, my.
And...
(Fitness Room, 4th floor)
- We must go to the fourth floor. - It's...
(Another long hike to the 4th floor)
- Is this the 3rd floor? - It's the 3rd floor.
Hold on. This is...
- Gosh, my water melted a lot. - Wait.
It's here.
Hey, I'm sweating a lot.
Gosh, we already did our workout.
- This is the place. - Let's go in. It's Jung Seo Woo.
- Jung Seo Woo? - Seo Woo.
- Oh, my. - There's a fitness room here.
- In a school? - This is no joke.
He's not here.
This place is nice.
(At the end of the hills and stairs...)
(lies a workout paradise, the fitness room.)
I didn't know there was a fitness room in a school.
- Gosh, look. I'm sweating. - My gosh.
By the way, where's our Whenever Guest?
Our Whenever Guest must have asked us...
- to come during the lunch break. - I guess so.
It has to be a student then.
No. Schoolteachers must also eat lunch.
Of course, but... He must be here.
I heard knocking.
- Gosh, they're students. - They're students.
(Smiling)
My gosh. Look at these students.
- Hello. - Are you Jung Seo Woo?
- I see. - You're Seo Woo.
Our Whenever Guests were students.
Right? I got the feeling that they would be students.
Should we move one down?
Hello.
I watched the movie trailer.
- It's an honor. - The one for "Hope?"
- Yes, "Hope." - "Hope."
Na Hong Jin's "Hope."
- I'm a fan of Na Hong Jin's works. - What?
I'm a fan of his works.
- Really? - Yes.
- Jung Min... - Did you watch all of his movies?
- I couldn't watch all of them. - I see. Right.
- I'm not old enough for some. - Exactly.
Right. He's strict about the age restrictions.
When we were coming up...
(The hill was incredibly steep.)
There were so many stairs.
So it feels like we're working out our legs when we come to school.
Right?
It's definitely a good workout.
Our classmates hate the stairs. They loathe the stairs.
Right?
Some of them want to take the stairs to the founder and complain.
(Their walk to school triggers complaints.)
Hold on. We're in the Fitness Room.
Do you do club activities here?
- Tell us about this place. - What is this place?
This fitness room used to be for our school athletic club.
But we got permission from our gym teacher,
so we get to work out here from time to time.
That's why we're here.
(They got permission to use it as they love working out.)
Anyway, we read your letter earlier.
You wrote that you worked with pens during the day...
and workout equipment during the night.
- Steel. - That must be why. Your build...
I mean, you guys have a nice build.
My gosh. You suddenly lifted your chest.
Chan Hwi.
Why did you lift your chest when I mentioned working out?
No. The bench is slanted.
I guess you work out a lot.
I bet you can lift some serious weight.
- Gosh, no. - No?
I have a bad back.
(I see.)
Already?
But why did you say that you worked out a lot in the letter?
As for the introduction letter...
So we've been in the same class since seventh grade.
- The three of you? - Yes.
Back then, we used to go...
to Internet cafes, not the gym.
We're happy when we enter the Internet cafes.
But the reality sinks in by the time you walk.
Then with Joon Ho's recommendation,
we started to work out at the gym since eighth grade.
- Are you in different classes now? - Yes, we are.
- But we still get lunch together. - I see.
(They're glued to each other even when working out.)
(Post-workout)
As we move up in grades, we have to attend more academies...
- and our study load increases. - Right.
We only get to see each other at the gym.
Actually, we wrote to your show before graduating middle school.
You wrote to our show in middle school.
But we came to you when you started high school.
(Their luck came rather late.)
We came to them in tenth grade.
You must be quite flustered.
- A bit. - Right?
So a year ago,
they watched our show and wrote the letter.
- They were excited for it. - Right.
They probably thought their story wasn't picked...
and were going to focus on their studies.
Then all of a sudden, our staff reached out to you.
We came to you out of the blue when you didn't have any spare time.
That's right.
Exactly. We're sorry about that.
- It's okay. - We didn't know.
- How are your studies going? - Are you studying a lot?
He gets the highest grades among us.
- Seo Woo. - He's ranked third in our grade.
(Ranked 3rd)
- That's amazing. - Why are you bringing up grades?
Let's listen to them.
No, don't bring up grades.
Let's talk about grades. He's ranked third.
Kids are stressed out the most by their grades.
How can we stop after hearing that he's ranked third?
If he's ranked third,
they must be ranked 4th and 5th.
(Why would you ask them that?)
Forget it. They're still growing. They're sweet kids.
- It's cute they wrote to the show. - "They're still growing."
- Seriously. - "They're sweet kids."
Joon Ho, can I ask you about your grades?
- I'm somewhere in the middle. - Okay.
What about you, Chan Hwi?
- I'm somewhere around 100th place. - That's great.
- What? - You need pretty good grades then.
Then it's slightly higher.
- You know what? That's great. - Right.
- There's much room to improve then. - Yes.
- You're only in tenth grade. - Right.
You can improve your grades if you set your mind to it.
Besides, you might not want to do anything that requires good grades.
But it does.
All right then.
If that's the case,
- you have to study. - Okay.
You should be studying a lot, Chan Hwi.
- What's your dream career? - Good luck, Chan Hwi.
I'm interested in psychology.
Psychology?
He's very thoughtful.
- I bet. - He is.
Do you read a lot of books, Chan Hwi?
No, I barely read books.
You keep asking about the exact opposites.
- You... Listen. - Be quiet, Jung Min.
Reverse whatever you want to ask.
Okay. Come on.
Is there a body part you want to show off?
- My arms. - Show us your arms.
(Impressed)
Your biceps look amazing.
Joon Ho seems happy about his arms.
Anyway, we're here today.
We should make good high school memories.
Right. They're our first Whenever Guests...
of our fifth season.
- That's right. - I want to give them many presents.
Ho Yeon and Jung Min are joining us today.
I look forward to seeing their competitive side.
So the fifth season comes with a new chance for you.
(A new rule for the season)
(Spare Chance)
It's a new rule for the fifth season.
- Whenever Guests... - Right.
get one spare chance.
But the options aren't all good.
Some of the options work against you.
But it will be a random draw.
(It depends on the Whenever Guests.)
Probability-wise, there are more lucky chances than unlucky ones.
If you want to use this spare chance when the time is right,
- feel free to do so. - Yes.
Here's the first one.
When you crush it, you'll see what the present is.
- Here you go, Chan Hwi. - It hasn't been long.
(Grabbing)
So he could eat it?
- It's edible. - Is that edible?
- It's edible. - It's edible.
It's just food coloring.
"Our muscles are ready."
"This is a symbolic brand for gym rats."
"Can we wear this brand now?"
"Three outfits from Under Armour."
This is a famous brand, right?
The combined weight of the 3 major drills must reach 500kg to wear it.
(The ultimate workout brand)
The 3 of you can get 1 outfit each.
Working out in that during summer will be great.
(Ping-Pong on Dumbbells)
(With 10 table tennis balls,)
(they must hit the target balls on top of the dumbbells.)
(Round 1: 2 target balls)
But they're much farther.
- Why are they so much farther? - How are we going to do this?
We can use up to ten balls.
(They must knock down 2 target balls.)
We just have to knock down those two balls.
It must bounce at least once. And the time limit is 30 seconds.
- Okay. - There's a time limit too?
Let's practice.
- I can lean over, right? - Yes.
That's allowed.
That's not good.
Gosh, this is hard.
It gets harder after the second bounce.
- You try it, Ho Yeon. - It's not easy.
Practice several times.
(Ho Yeon starts practicing.)
Not even close.
This one is hard.
Hey, this is going to be tough.
No.
- They can do it. - We have to get the hang of it.
You got this.
- Just a bit... - You must find your own zero point.
Try to bring it closer to you.
- Closer to me? Me? - You know what?
I think it will work if you land it around here.
- Like this? - Yes.
Okay. I think I got it.
- Here. - That's it.
Nice.
(The ball hits the spot recommended by Jung Min.)
(Success)
- Nice. Find your own zero point. - You got it, right?
(I got the hang of it.)
- Find your own zero point. - There you go.
The zero point that matches your throw and power.
- Right. - Yes.
It's somewhere around here.
- You got it. - It was around here.
- Right here. It was here. - Here.
- The shot group is here. - Here.
- Right there. - Here.
- Here... - Let me get ready first.
(Jung Min practices hitting the sweet spot too.)
That's too high.
Darn it.
Why is the trajectory crooked?
(Laughing)
- What? - It's very crooked.
- I think he's getting angry. - He can't stay calm.
Right. He can't hold back now.
Darn it.
- What? How did that happen? - Calm down.
- Wait. This is only... - Darn it.
- This is only Round One. - My gosh.
"Stop it."
It works out when you least expect it.
- All right. - The balls...
We have ten balls.
- Let's do 3, 3, 2, and 2. - Right. We'll take 2.
- You can take three. - Yes.
Ho Yeon, you can take three too.
Okay. I got three.
- Let's do a group cheer. - How about a group cheer?
- All right. - One, two, three.
- Let's go! - Let's go! Great.
- Should I go first? - Why don't we go in this order?
- Yes. - Let's go in this order.
I got this.
Here I go.
Ready.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
(The 1st try of the 1st mission in the new season)
(First try)
Just do one.
Darn it. That was close.
Knock down at least one.
Just one.
That was so close!
- Gosh. - No!
We have time.
- Just knock down 1. - Just 1.
Just one.
(Precisely targeting the sweet spot)
I need to knock down both. How many seconds?
Five, four...
(First try failed)
That was hard.
- This is hard. - Darn it.
- We have to do it here, right? - Yes.
- This is hard. - It's very hard.
Stay behind the line, but you can lean forward a bit.
It's harder than you think.
It's flying up high.
- That's it. You threw it too hard. - I threw it too hard.
It'd be nice if we could decide how many times we'll let it bounce.
(His throw was too weak this time.)
(None of the shots are hitting the target.)
(What are we going to do?)
Jung Min, take a break and try again.
Wait. You did it.
(Clearing both targets)
- All right. That's it. - He got this.
You found your sweet spot.
- Jung Min practices a lot. - You got it.
Remember this feeling.
- He got both. - Jung Min.
You found your sweet spot.
All right. Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's do a group cheer.
- All right. - One, two, three.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Who wants to go first? - Me.
- Ho Yeon, you go first. - Okay.
- You got this. - I got this.
Got this.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 2.)
Let them know you're starting.
- Here I go. - Set.
(Second try)
- When it's the real thing... - You threw it a bit too hard.
That's it!
It's hard to adjust your power when it's the real thing.
That's the spot.
It was right there.
I got it.
- Nice. - All right.
(He hits one target ball.)
All right.
We just need to knock down one more.
- Let's do this. - Jae Seok, just one more.
Just one more.
- That's it! Jung Min. - All right, Jung Min.
- Jung Min, just 1 more. - Jung Min, just 1 more.
Jung Min, just one more.
(They can complete Round 1 if he hits 1 more target ball.)
- Jung Min, just one more. - Please.
(The last player, Hwang Jung Min)
Five seconds, Jung Min.
Four, three...
Four...
(Bullseye)
Yes!
(Thrilled)
(Flawlessly completing the mission)
I crushed it!
- Okay. We did it. - I crushed it.
- Round One is complete. - Okay. It's complete.
(Feeling proud)
- Gosh, Mr. Hope. - He finished it in five seconds.
It wasn't easy to pull it off in five seconds.
- It was tough. - He had a spare ball too.
Then we can have 11 balls for the next one, right?
They don't get accumulated.
You must decide whether you want to keep going or stop.
We have eight tries left and a spare chance.
We completed Round 1 in 2 tries.
All right. One, two, three.
- Go. - Great.
You read it, Chan Hwi.
It's in the cookie.
Chan Hwi is sweating the most.
Why is he sweating? He's not the one playing the game.
- Chan Hwi is nervous. - Chan Hwi...
Round Two.
"A hip fashion item that will attract our friends' attention."
"Three pairs of sneakers from Salomon."
- Gosh, they look great. - Look at the sneakers.
(Looking stylish)
They look great.
- Nice. - That's a popular brand, right?
- We love them. Yes. - You like them?
- We love them. - You could wear them to school.
Tell us about Round Two.
(Round 2)
(3 target balls)
- Will they get higher? - They'll adjust the height.
(Adding a platform to the back row)
- Three... - We get the same number of balls?
Ten balls and thirty seconds.
It's still 30 seconds, right?
We get 10 balls and 30 seconds, but 3 target balls.
But we might get lucky...
and knock them down in one go, right?
- That's a possibility. - Right.
My gosh. This is totally doable.
We might be able to knock down...
- two in one go. - Right.
See? This is what I mean.
- All right. - Just like that.
- That's what you need to do. - That's it.
I used up my luck!
I feel like my luck is over now.
- Do what you just did. - Great.
- Should we go for it now? - Okay.
- Now? Remember this feeling. - Let's go.
- You'll go first. - Go.
- Okay. - You take three.
- All right. Go. - You go first.
- Round Three. - Help us, deity of variety shows.
No, I mean, this is our third try.
All right. Here I go.
Ready. Set...
(Ho Yeon got the hang of it.)
(Third try)
Do what you did earlier.
- Gosh. - My gosh.
(She quickly lost her touch.)
- It's okay. - Jung Min.
- Gosh. - My gosh.
Oh, no.
- My gosh. Nice. - We still have a shot.
(He precisely hits one target ball.)
- Nice. - I'll knock down just one.
I'll knock down one.
Just one!
Jae Seok, just one more!
(They can complete Round 2 if he hits 1 target ball.)
Just one more!
Five, four...
(Third try)
I'll knock down one.
Just one!
(Third try)
Jae Seok, just one more!
(They can complete Round 2 if he hits 1 target ball.)
Just one more!
Five, four...
My gosh!
Three...
What was that?
I told you not to mess it up on purpose...
- for the show. - Why would I mess it up...
- on purpose? - Jung Min.
- Going last is quite tough. - Why would I do that?
After I failed,
I felt an intense gaze, so I turned around.
"What was that?"
Come on.
- Jung Min got the hang of it. - He's doing well.
Let's give him more balls.
- Should we? - No.
- Right. He should get more. - No. Let's stick to the same thing.
- Jae Seok and I can take only one. - No, that's not it.
- You should... - Then...
No.
- Hold on. Ho Yeon. - That's great.
- Then... - You and I...
- couldn't even hit one. - Right. Let's do this then.
- It's not that. - Ho Yeon. We'll take...
- only 1. - We'll take 1.
- The good ones will take 4. - They'll take 4.
- No. - This is the right strategy.
- This is the right strategy. - One, one, three, and five.
(Please come to an amicable agreement.)
- Let's do that. - One, one, four, and four.
- Right? - Yes.
- Yes. Let's go with that. - All right. We'll take one each.
This is the right call, isn't it?
- This is the right call. - Yes.
- It is. - Then you can take one.
This is hurting my pride.
Gosh, this is hurting my pride.
- You got this! - Let's go!
- We got this. - So...
Let's do this.
I just need to knock down one.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 5.)
- Let them know before you start. - Okay.
All right. Here I go!
Ready. Set...
(Jung Min got the hang of it.)
(You got this.)
Set...
(Fifth try)
- Nice. - Okay.
That's it. Good.
One more.
Good. Well done.
(Jung Min hit one ball.)
That was good.
One. Just one.
It's...
Okay!
- Okay! - Yes!
(As expected from Yoo One Shot)
(Cheering)
(That's it!)
Good job.
(Cheering)
- Well done. - Unbelievable.
Well done.
- Good job. - That was nerve-racking.
- Round Two, success! - Success!
- Our strategy... - Right?
- Well done. - Knowing there were players...
- after me felt reassuring. - Good.
- It was the reassurance. - That was nice.
Now then.
We have 6, 7, 8, 9, and 10 tries left.
- We even have the chance. - Exactly.
- All right, Round Three. - By the way,
the game gets way harder.
- It's okay. - So...
if we fail, you'll lose everything.
- It's okay. - No.
It's not okay.
- Draw a chance, - Okay.
see the result,
and then decide whether to go or stop.
- They can't. - You can't do that.
- Jung Min. - They can't draw one...
- before making the decision. - Is that so?
But the guest picks one.
- Come on. - So it's a no.
- Go? - What?
- What about you? - Go or stop.
- Okay, go or stop. - Make up your mind.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Go! - Of course.
- All right. - Things don't look bad.
"The number one thing to save up for..."
"to track every workout in detail."
"Two Galaxy Watches and one Apple Watch."
(Unbelievable!)
Smartwatches?
(Heavy)
Why is one of them different?
Won't the guys fight over it?
- The phone they use. - It depends on the phone.
- I see. - They found out in advance.
- Just don't say anything. - I'm sorry. I didn't know.
The boys won't fight over it.
They use different phone models.
(Round 3)
(6 target balls)
- Five? - Five?
- Oh, my gosh. - What?
- Probably three rows. - It's technically bowling.
Right?
- But... - We can't aim at them...
one at a time.
One stone must kill two birds.
- Try it, Ho Yeon. - Let's give Ho Yeon more balls.
- Me? - Yes, this time...
- Okay. - Let's try four this time.
Okay. I'll give it a shot.
It's okay.
Ho Yeon, how about just two?
- Four seems a lot. - Right.
- It's too much. - Yes, it's too much.
- Ho Yeon. - Guys!
- Let's go with two, Ho Yeon. - Didn't you have faith in me?
Just two, okay?
No, but I...
Giving you an extra ball shows how much faith we have in you.
- No, but I... - Giving you an extra ball shows...
- Just two. - how much faith we have in you.
- How about three? - Three sounds good.
- Yes, three. - Okay.
The boys were like...
(2 is enough.)
- Three. - Ho Yeon gets three.
- Okay. - Two.
Three, four,
one. Good?
- I get the most? - Yes.
- Okay. - Yeon Seok is the best at it.
- I'm in. - Two, three, four, one.
Two, three, four, and one. Let's go.
Here we go. Round 3 and the 6th try.
Here I go!
Ready. Set.
(Sixth try)
- That's it. - Good.
- She's on a roll. - That's it.
Ho Yeon got a lot.
(Hit 2 balls)
(Investing 2 balls in Ho Yeon paid off.)
Ho Yeon got a lot.
- Why is it still here? - Get lost.
- That's it. - Yes.
We're on a roll today.
- Hold on. - It's okay.
(Yeon Seok only succeeded 1 with 4 balls.)
Yeon Seok?
(Sixth try)
Just one.
Five seconds left.
- Why is the time... - Four...
(There's only one more chance left.)
It's a tough one to finish.
- Bounce it hard. - One.
Three.
(Sixth try failed)
- It was a tough one to finish. - Exactly.
Let's use the chance here!
- We'll use it now. - Okay.
- The chance? You can use it. - Go ahead.
- Let's use it. - Okay.
We need to change things up.
- Totally. - I agree.
Nice timing.
There's a chance that's a dud...
or like a penalty in here.
Try to pick a good one.
- Which one? - Whichever you want.
- Just avoid the bad one. - Trust your gut.
Yes. Don't pick the bad one.
- Okay. - Read it out loud for us.
- What is it? - "The ace..."
"takes on this try alone."
- Does the ace try alone? - All ten balls?
Then...
Why don't you three discuss...
- and pick 1 ace? - Pick 1 member.
- This is for the better. - Really?
- One should throw all the balls. - True.
- Totally. - Jung Min has a knack for it.
- No way. - He has a knack for it.
Give him some trust.
Are you trying to impress them? Come here.
What's with you out of the blue? Stop it.
- Watch. I've got it in me. - No, Jae Seok.
- Stop it. - I've got it in me as well.
- No. - You don't, Jae Seok.
You're suited as the MC.
- Seriously. - Now then.
- To think I'd be... - Jae Seok is...
- I feel a burden. - I'll make up for it one day.
Give the ball to the ace.
- Okay. - The one who gets it...
will play the game.
- Come over here. - One of us.
Give the ball to the ace.
(Candidate 1: Down with Round 3 Jung Ho Yeon)
(Candidate 2: Upper-body specialist Yoo Yeon Seok)
(Candidate 3: Passion-filled Hwang Jung Min)
(Candidate 4: Just Yu Jae Seok)
(Ace Hwang Jung Min)
I thought he was giving it to me.
It wasn't you, Jae Seok.
- You're suited as the MC. - I was going to...
- snatch it from him. - I thought it was me.
- All right. - I thought it was me...
- for getting 2 earlier. - Wasp gets 10 balls.
Wasp.
- Are you going for it? - Practice first.
No, I'm going for it.
- Go for it. - Go for it.
- Good luck! - Good luck!
The seventh try. Ready.
(The seventh try using the ace chance)
Call it.
I know, okay?
- Don't lose your temper. Okay? - Got it.
- He's just telling you. - I was concentrating.
He's just telling you.
Here I go!
Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 7.)
(Seventh try)
That's it.
Too strong.
(Seventh try)
We made the wrong decision.
(Remaining targets: 4)
- Hit 2 birds with 1 stone. - Right.
- It's okay. - Five seconds left.
(Seventh try)
- Hit 2 birds with 1 stone. - Right.
- It's okay. - Five seconds left.
Four, three...
(Seventh try failed)
It's a hard one.
Three.
It's hard.
(The ace chance is gone now.)
It's infuriating, right?
- It's a hard one. - It's hard.
Ho Yeon, be the coach of this try...
- and decide how many each. - Go ahead.
Jung Min already did it once.
Here's what I think.
Three, three, three, and one.
(3 balls, 3 balls, 1 ball, 3 balls)
- Good idea. - Right?
- Three, three, three, and one. - Yes.
Okay. Today...
I'm holding back today.
- We still have a try left. - Right.
Ho Yeon.
- Three, three... - It was based on the result.
- True. - Right?
The 3-3-3-1 formation.
- Okay. - I hit two balls.
- What about the order? - The 3-3-3-1 formation?
(Activated the 3-3-3-1 formation)
- Okay. - And the order?
First off... I had a good feeling...
- when I went first. - First.
First, second, third,
- and last. - Last one.
I'll make history with this one ball.
- Okay. - Now then.
- Let's cheer. - Okay.
- Two tries. - We only have two tries left.
- It's... - You get nervous on the last try...
- and usually fail. - We must succeed.
- In one... - We must.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's do this! - Let's do this!
The people ahead of me.
- Finish it, please. - Focus.
Let me move this.
Now the real game begins.
- Here I go. - The ninth try. Ready.
Set.
(Ninth try)
(1 shot, 2 kills)
Keep going.
(Off to a great start)
(Ninth try)
- I have to keep going. - The time is ticking.
- I'm sorry. - Okay.
- Okay. - Well done.
(Hit 3 balls)
- They'll make it. - Please.
Good. Nice one.
Okay.
- They'll make it. - Please.
(Ninth try)
Even just one.
One left.
(There's only one left.)
- We can make it. - One.
(The last target)
(Two players are left.)
One.
We can make it.
- One. - Five, four...
(Ninth try)
(Jae Seok's last ball)
Three, two...
(I'll make history with this one ball.)
- One. - A buzzer beater!
(A buzzer beater!)
(Ninth try failed)
- One. - A buzzer beater!
Gosh, Jae Seok!
(That was so close.)
Seriously!
Still...
Really.
How did that one ball last?
I think we can use the 3-3-3-1 formation...
- again. - If only it had hit here.
Seriously, why couldn't we succeed?
That one ball you have feels like such a waste.
It's such a waste.
Come on.
I'll throw two balls.
This time...
We'll stick with 3-3-3-1, but I'll throw the last ball.
From what I can see,
we'll succeed within ten balls.
(Jae Seok is given 3 balls.)
- Let's give it a shot. - Okay.
It's our last try. Gather up.
- Really. - For goodness' sake.
(The last try of Round 3)
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Split up the balls.
The last try.
It's fine even if they fail.
Yes, it's fine.
But we should succeed.
- Don't worry. - True.
Let's go.
The last try.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on the last try.)
- Call it. - I will.
Here I go.
Ready.
Set...
(Last try)
Nice.
(1 shot)
(2 kills)
- Nice. - More to the left.
If only someone could...
(Last try)
- Hold on. - That one.
- It counts, right? - Yes.
- It counts. - Yes, it counts.
(There are only 2 target balls left.)
Okay.
(Jae Seok hit a whopping 4 balls.)
- Good. - That one counts, right?
- Yes, it counts. - Hold on. Get rid of it.
(Last try)
One last ball.
- One last ball. - Nice.
I think it'll work.
One ball.
(One ball!)
Please.
(Only one ball left)
(Last try)
Please.
Please, Yeon Seok.
(The last hope)
- Why must I finish the last one? - Jung Min.
- Watch the time. - Five seconds left.
- Jung Min, please. - Jung Min.
- Five seconds left. - Watch the time.
- You can do it. - Jung Min.
Four, three, two...
(The end)
It's a memory worth keeping.
That was so close.
- What a bummer. - It was a hard one.
Well done, everyone.
That was so close.
- That was so close. - No.
(The Prize Retrieval Team is on the move.)
(The sweatsuits, sneakers, and smartwatches are gone.)
Are you taking them?
Good job.
- No. - It's okay.
- Don't worry about it. - Jung Min.
How you took them is annoying.
On purpose.
What a real bummer.
When you practice...
- That was so close. - Really close.
It was...
You see,
we forgot that we're at a school.
I really wanted to win it.
Let's at least give these out.
- They looked so happy. - I'm sorry.
- Thank you. - I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Goodness.
It's a clock.
We'll hang it up in the classroom.
(A clock instead of smartwatches)
Things were going so well today.
No, it's still good.
They have to go to class now.
- It's a memorable day. - Really?
Good job, everyone. It was an honor.
- Study hard. - Thank you.
- Well done. - Gosh.
- I feel bad. - The strategy wasn't bad at all.
Yu Jae Seok, Yoo Yeon Seok,
Hwang Jung Min, and Jung Ho Yeon.
I'm a real fan of them. But it was kind of...
Well, it was...
Can I start again?
No, just go with it.
We'll keep working hard,
get perfect scores in the CSAT,
and meet Yu Jae Seok again...
in "You Quiz on the Block."
Whenever possible,
- post-workout. - Post-workout.
(The students have left for class.)
- This feels... - That was...
It left a weird aftertaste.
A feeling I can't put into words.
But really.
If you had hit the last ball,
- it would've been amazing. - For real.
The ball was so close.
What a shame.
- It was by a hair. - Exactly.
- We... - What time do we meet...
the next guest?
We meet them at 3:10pm.
We need to get lunch fast.
How about this?
Since we're at a school, why don't we get some street food?
- I'm in. - I don't mind anything.
Is that so? Ramyeon is...
- Don't you like ramyeon? - I love it.
How do ramyeon and gimbap sound?
- Street food, is it? - This gimbap place.
- Yes? - Yes.
- The one around the corner? - Yes.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Ho Yeon wants it.
(Street food as recommended by Ho Yeon)
It was a real bummer.
- Gosh. - The view here is...
It's nice even looking at it a second time.
(A breathtaking view amid the bittersweet moment)
If we saw this view after succeeding in the last round,
- we'd have been over the moon. - It would've been great.
I want to play a game again.
- We will soon. - We will soon.
I meant, play it now.
I may have become addicted.
- Our lunch bet. - Sorry?
- Our lunch bet. - Let's do that at the restaurant.
Okay.
I have two games in mind.
Please pick 1 of the 2.
- Two? - Did In Sung give you an idea?
The game In Sung suggested was...
to stop the stopwatch,
and the one...
- with the lowest time buys lunch. - Right.
- Yes. - This is the game I played...
with Director Hwang Dong Hyuk...
and the production team while filming "Squid Game."
You played several games...
- during work. - I did.
- What is it? - It's called the Crocodile Game.
- That one? - The game where you push a tooth,
- and the crocodile shuts its mouth. - Isn't there an app?
- Yes. - Right?
We played that game to see...
who would treat everyone to coffee.
There's an app.
Let's download it.
I already have it on my phone.
- Isn't this the place? - We're here.
Can we go in?
Isn't it closed?
- No. - It looks open.
- I was craving ramyeon. - Hi.
Street food in front of schools is great.
- Hi. - Are you open?
Rabokki also sounds nice.
- Did you bring a ball? - How about rabokki?
(Brought a ball in frustration)
What kind of gimbap do you like?
Aged kimchi and spicy chili.
Spicy chili sounds good.
I'm feeling rabokki.
- Order it. - One rabokki...
- Rabokki? - for sure. We can share it.
Ma'am, can we order kimchi noodles?
Yes, you can.
- Then... - One kimchi noodles.
I'd like Chapagetti.
Let's get pork cutlet to share.
- I'm in. - One pork cutlet.
- Nice. - One gimbap.
- Okay. - I want...
- Let's order individual dishes now. - I...
I'd like an egg ramyeon.
Egg ramyeon.
Should I have kimchi ramyeon?
All Ho Yeon has in mind is ramyeon.
- I... - Do you not have it regularly?
- Is it filling? - My nickname is Noodle Jung.
- I love noodles. - You do?
- Then... - Are you Whenever Possible?
Yes, ma'am. So you know the show.
Where were you just now?
- Daewon High School. - Daewon High School.
We failed Round Three.
- What did you want, Jung Min? - We're all upset.
I need to use the restroom. Where is it, ma'am?
To get to the restroom, turn when you see the building...
- Look, Ho Yeon. - and...
there's one downstairs.
(Floating in midair)
Did you bring one with you?
It was my go-to as a kid.
(Copying right away)
That's it.
(Laughing)
Let's stop for now.
Looks like you two are still pretty disappointed.
It's just that...
What we wanted was to hit the ball...
at the buzzer...
and taste victory.
- Yes. - It was a hard one.
Now that Director Na Hong Jin's "Hope" has been released,
- "The Wailing" is on TV a lot. - True.
- I see it everywhere. - True.
Ho Yeon, was it two years ago?
I remember you telling me...
you were working out to be able to carry a gun.
Ho Yeon went through a lot. Here's why.
- The car Stellar is in the movie. - Yes, that car.
It's a really old one, no?
We asked around and bought every Stellar possible...
in the country.
You bought them?
One car wasn't enough.
There were 11 of them.
- All of them were manual. - Right.
All the Stellars were manual.
- Ho Yeon... - Did you get a license?
- Yes. - I only had a regular license.
- So I got the manual one. - She got another license.
Getting one is hard now.
(After getting her license,)
(she mastered high-difficulty driving herself...)
(and boldly performed the intense driving scenes.)
(High-level action scenes that took a long time to bring to life)
(She created another iconic character.)
The Crocodile Game.
Shall we play it?
- No? - Should we?
You must really enjoy playing games.
There was a reason she was cast for "Squid Game."
You're right.
Ho Yeon is a big fan of games.
- I do love games. - "Squid Game" is about games.
She's a former gamer.
- Isn't it exciting? - Let's give it a try.
How about the one who gets bitten is out?
- Or the game will end too soon. - Okay.
- The order... - Go first, Ho Yeon.
- Got it. I'll go first. - Okay.
(Tapping)
It's better to get bitten early.
- Only then are you out. - Right.
Bite me.
This feels about right.
- Okay. - Gosh.
Yes!
(Relieved)
- Okay. - Gosh.
(Disappointed)
Gosh. He made it.
Whoever gets bitten will get saved.
- When there are two left, - Okay.
- the bitten one will pay. - I got it.
- Why do you go first? - Aren't I the first one?
- Why do you go first? - Why?
The last game ended here.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Let's do that.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Scissors.
I'll go first.
(Yeon Seok)
I need to make it out.
(Yeon Seok, Ho Yeon)
It's a good thing to get bitten, so we press it with ease.
(Yeon Seok)
(Ho Yeon)
I'm sorry. That was loud.
Is it just the two of us?
(The two face off.)
- Now, the bitten one... - The bitten one will pay now.
But it's okay to push more than one tooth.
I like that.
(Adding an exciting rule)
- Good. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
You'll push...
- Wait. Let's order more. - Exactly.
- They'll order more. - We wanted fried dumplings.
- Ma'am, we'll get fried dumplings. - Okay.
(The final match begins.)
- I can push more than one, right? - Yes, you can.
Okay.
Gosh. You're bold.
- Ma'am. - I can relax at first.
(1 tooth, 2 teeth)
What?
Hold on. I'm going to push one more tooth.
(One more)
(Interesting)
(1 tooth)
(Should I go for one more?)
No, I'll stop here.
That's enough for now.
- Push one more. - No, that was enough.
- Come on. Go for one more. - No, that was enough.
- That was... - That was enough. Yes.
(Thinking)
Okay.
(Yeon Seok has to pay.)
(Jae Seok has made it out.)
Yeon Seok, thanks for lunch.
- Thanks for lunch. - Thank you.
- Thanks for the meal. - Thank you.
It's here. Gosh. Thank you.
You're cooking alone, but you're really fast.
Gosh. It's been a while...
since I had snack food in front of a school.
(The best snack food combination is here.)
- Thank you. - Gosh. They're served at once.
Gosh. It looks tasty.
- Guess which is jjajang noodles. - This one.
- Right. It's steamy. - It was obvious.
- It was the steamy one. - This one had to be the one.
I crave cold kimchi noodles in summer.
Thanks for the food. Please enjoy.
Please enjoy. Thanks for the food.
Gosh. Look at this rabokki.
- It's been a while since I had it. - You can't take all the noodles.
I'll take this much. I grabbed too much.
- That's not fair. - Jae Seok.
We only have one rabokki.
I was going to shake some off, but it didn't work.
(Taking a fair amount)
I'll have the dumplings first.
I need to taste this first.
(Satisfied)
Gosh.
It's tasty.
- Is the sauce different? - Yes.
(Jung Min tries a bite of the pork cutlet first.)
- It's tasty. - Hey.
The pork cutlet is so good.
Is it?
I think she made the sauce herself.
Gosh. You and the sauce.
He's into the sauce again.
He's Hwang Sauce.
- Is the sauce different? - Yes.
- I think she made it from scratch. - I see.
It's good.
(Surprised)
- Right? - It's sweet.
(It's been a while since they had the snack near a school)
(At that moment,)
(someone quietly starts digging in.)
(Noodle Jung)
At golf clubs...
(She only targets the noodles.)
- Gosh. It's good. - I'm full.
- I'm done. - I know.
(While the others start to put their chopsticks down,)
(Noodle Jung starts the second half.)
She does love to have noodles.
I'm Noodle Jung.
(Noodle Jung lives up to her name.)
Once you're into noodles...
Gosh. It was tasty.
Ho Yeon is a noodle-lover too.
Gosh. I loved it.
It's been a while to have these street snacks.
- I'll pay now. - Okay.
I loved the food.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you, ma'am.
We need to wait five minutes.
(They'll get in a cab for the next one.)
You'll start greeting the audience in theaters.
I'll do that starting tomorrow.
For example, we also need to greet...
our viewers.
Today, we're in Jungnang-gu.
We go and see the viewers in each household.
"Nice to meet you."
"Thanks for watching."
(Dreaming of a meet-and-greet shyly)
- Did you just do a stage greeting? - Yes, I did.
- This is a stage, then. - Yes.
We have a stage.
- Were you watching our show? - Do it over here.
- Thank you. - There really is a stage.
Let's invite our two guests from "Hope."
(Entering the stage right away)
Hello.
- Their movie was released. - Well, they are...
- It was released on July 15. - Yes.
Please tell us about your roles.
I played Beom Seok, a police station chief.
- Thank you. - Okay.
I'm Jung Ho Yeon, and I play Officer Lim Sung Ae.
- Gosh. Our cab is here. - Yes.
- You can hop in. - Okay.
We'll move to the next stage.
- Thanks. - Hello.
- I'll sit in the back. - Gosh. It's nice and cold.
Goodness.
- I think this is it. - Yes, it was here.
- You found this one, right? - Yes.
- Isn't this place cute? - It's cute.
- It's cute, right? - There's more space inside.
Hello.
Jung Min, get some.
(They'll drink some coffee because they have 20 minutes.)
Let's play a game for this one too.
(Game)
- A game? - Yes.
- Gosh. You're addicted to games. - Can't we play a game for this?
- Sure. - But for this one...
(Game)
- Let's play Pick a Card. - Pick a Card?
- Pick a Card. - We have to hide our cards.
- But I don't have a credit card. - What is Pick a Card?
- I pay with my phone too. - Really?
- In that case... - Since we are the same...
Then we can mix these up like this.
- Then what do we do? - Give me the cards.
- Out of these four credit cards... - She's a game fanatic.
What do we do with them?
- We'll let her pick. - We'll let her pick...
to pay for the coffee.
- Who are we picking? - It's...
(A professional gamer versus a game noob)
- The clerk will choose. - Yes, when we pay.
Let's order quickly. We don't have much time.
- What are you having, Jung Min? - A Viennese coffee.
Okay. A Viennese coffee.
I'll get an iced Americano. Decaf, please.
Smoothies will take a while, right?
- Ten minutes? - No, it'll be done quickly.
- Is that so? - Yes. We don't have many customers.
Then I'll have a light decaf Americano.
- Why did you ask about smoothies? - It's easier to unify the orders.
- A light decaf Americano? - Yes.
- We'll get two. - Why don't we have some of those?
- Sounds good. - Something like this?
- Yes. - We'll also get the salt bread.
Why don't we buy them all for every staff?
Six breads, then?
- We'll get them all. - Six breads.
- Six chocolate salt bread? - Yes.
- It's good for the cafe. - Exactly.
- They made delicious ones. - They did.
Actually, we'll get six chocolate salt breads, and a red bean bun.
- I got it. - Yes, they do have red bean buns.
Okay.
- Is that all? - Yes, that's all.
We have four different types of credit cards.
Of the four options,
please choose one.
This one.
- Whose is it? - Jung Min.
(Jung Min)
What? Is that mine?
Sorry.
What's up with you?
I just chose one.
- Pay for it, Jung Min. - For goodness' sake.
(The red bean guy paid for it.)
- Thank you. - Yes, thanks. We'll enjoy it.
Gosh, Jung Min.
Goodness.
- Gosh, it's... - They packed the rest.
- Jung Min. - Yes?
(Chocolate salt bread)
It looks good.
I'm the boss.
(She was Noodle Jung before, and now she's Bread Jung.)
Inside is...
I'm so happy.
It tastes better because Jung Min bought it.
It's so tasty.
(Where is our second spare time they'll visit in a happy mood?)
It's very delicious.
It's three people.
Choi Ye Sun, Park Dong Rye and Park Ye Sun.
"They're my source of energy."
"Let me introduce my adorable students to you."
"Even when the dictation is hard, they keep smiling."
"They were overloaded with excitement..."
"to get an elementary school degree."
"They sing beautifully when singing the school anthem."
"Please bring another moment of joy to my students."
This is it. The J Building.
It's on the second floor.
(It's where the adorable students are.)
English tutor. This isn't it.
Night school. It's a night school.
It's a night school.
- For the elderly. - Yes, for the elderly.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Gosh. Hello.
- Hello. - Hello. Gosh.
Do we take off our shoes?
- No. - Keep them on.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you. Goodness.
(The second Whenever Guests)
(Park Ye Sun, Choi Ye Sun, Park Dong Rye)
- They are the Whenever Guests. - Gosh.
- I see. - It's an honor.
- Goodness. - Is this a night school?
He looks like a high school student.
- They are the Whenever Guests. - Gosh.
It's really nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
We are here now.
- I heard this is a night school. - Yes.
We study.
It's a school that teaches Hangul.
- Is that so? - Yes.
I see.
(It's a special school filled with the elderly's passion.)
- She's in the nighttime class. - I see.
I'm in the daytime class.
- I see. - From 12pm to 1:30pm.
- From 12pm to 1:30pm. - To 1:30pm.
Yes. From 12pm.
(The second spare time is the night school.)
You've been coming here for a while now, right?
- Since 2011. - It's been 15 years.
I think it was August.
- It's been 15 years. Gosh. - I came to learn Hangul.
Actually, if you couldn't read Hangul,
it could limit your everyday life.
- I bet it was difficult. - Yes.
Life must have gotten easier since you came here.
Gosh. It's better than good.
- What's the best part of it? - What?
At supermarkets,
if I were to buy detergent...
- Right. - I checked the picture to buy it...
because I couldn't read before.
- I see. - I see.
When we withdraw money, we have to write the slip.
- That's right. - So...
I brought the slip with me.
And I asked my husband or my son to fill in the blanks.
That was how I withdrew money.
Now, I can't withdraw money because I have none.
(An unexpected ending)
Back then, you couldn't withdraw money...
because you couldn't read.
Now, it's because you don't have money.
- Her balance is insufficient. - Right.
(Laughing)
If this is a night school...
(Ending the story with a fantastic laughter)
Is there a class president...
or a student body president?
- Yes. - She's the student body president.
- Are you the student president? - I see.
- You're the student president. - We didn't know.
If anything happens and if there's anything going on,
she prepares all this food.
- Did you boil these potatoes? - Yes.
It's for you to have.
Gosh. There are so many.
- Let's share and taste it. - Have it.
She peeled all the potatoes.
That's a lot of work.
- Share them with the staff. - Would you like some?
- Yes. Here. - They should have some.
- It looks so tasty. - On "Running Man,"
they give you lots of food.
You eat so well on that show.
- Yes. - So, I boiled the potatoes...
- to give them to you. - Thank you.
- Let's share. - You should use your hands.
- Your hands are from your mother. - Still...
- I want to try it too. - It's tasty.
- Is it good? - It's good.
- It's so good. - They look so tasty.
It's seasoned.
Yes, I added salt and finished it with some sugar.
(The sweet and savory combination and savory wakes them up.)
It's sweet and savory.
- It's really sweet and savory. - It's perfectly sweet.
- I could taste them both. - It's perfectly seasoned.
How do they get sweetened?
- These? - With salt...
After steaming the potatoes with water first,
I drain the water.
I sprinkle some sugar and toss the potatoes.
I put them in a pot, cover it with a lid, and toss them.
I add sugar again for those potatoes inside.
I give it a toss again.
Is it finished after some tossing?
Yes, that's the way to go.
- It's so good. - You're an unusual cook.
Seriously.
Take the call.
I'm going to see her later in the evening.
Why the heck does she call me?
She's curious.
Exactly. That's why she called.
(The student president's spicy comment)
- Now... - It's like watching a sitcom.
("Granny's Kick!")
Do you have grandchildren?
- This is so nice. - Yes, I do.
In that case,
your grandsons must text you a lot.
- They do text me. - Yes.
At first, I didn't know how to read it.
- When I got the text, - She's a talented cook.
- I did nothing. - Yesterday...
- Yes. - No, the day before yesterday,
- I told the producer girl, - Now,
- "I'll bring some potatoes." - I can read the texts.
- I can read texts now. - Yes.
That's a big step already.
- It must be fun... - Yes.
- to talk to your grandchildren. - While watching "Running Man..."
What is this conversation?
In the beginning,
- when I first studied Hangul, - When I watched it...
- they said, "Grandma," - Yes.
"one hit for every wrong answer."
They hit me on the palm.
How did you get to send...
your stories to our show?
Did you write and send it yourself?
- She did it. - Did you ask your teacher?
- I see. She's your teacher. - I see.
She's the teacher. Gosh. Hello.
- Did you ask her? Or did she do it? - Yes.
Why did you want to be the guest?
We wanted to try it.
(Simple)
But you said you didn't think much about it.
- I didn't think about it, but... - Right.
(It was strikingly clear.)
- Our teachers are the best. - Yes, they are the best.
When I ask my kids,
they'd answer me once.
But if I ask them twice,
- they get annoyed. - They don't answer us.
- They won't even respond. - But our teachers here...
- All kids are like that. - Yes.
Gosh. He knows.
I'd ask them several times,
but our teachers always answer kindly.
- Why? - Why do sons and daughters do that?
I'm also a son, but I don't understand it either.
When it comes to learning, do it with a stranger.
- Not your kids. - Never your kids.
- It can't be your husband either. - That's true.
- You're right about it. - I love this school so much.
- You're right. - Yes.
You have asked us to come during this spare time.
What is this spare time for?
It's break time.
- I see. - In the evening,
- we have to study. - You come to the night school.
We usually rest at home and come.
But today, we'll shoot this and study later on.
It'll be 9:30pm when we go back home.
We heard that someone got...
- an elementary school diploma. - I did.
(Overloaded with excitement to get an elementary school diploma)
- When I was young, - Yes.
- I was poor. - Okay.
- So I couldn't study. - I see.
I lived like that for over 50 years.
The woman I worked with said,
"Ye Sun, since you'll get some rest because your back hurts,"
"why don't you start studying?"
She talked me into it.
Because of that, I came here and started studying.
- That was what happened. - And then,
I studied several years...
- to take the test. - I see.
But I couldn't pass it at once. I took it three times.
- I took the test three times. - I see.
And I passed it.
The rain was pouring.
There's the Seoul Office of Education.
- Yes. - I went there.
I was thrilled to get the diploma, so in the rain,
I cried my eyes out.
We went there together.
- Did you go there with her? - We went together.
(She could still vividly feel...)
(the joy of getting the diploma.)
I love studying so much.
- I see. - I know the things I didn't know.
- It's fun to get to know things. - Yes.
- You love that so much. - Yes.
The best thing about learning to read...
is that it makes me more confident in everyday life.
We can respond with confidence.
- We are confident. - When we're lost...
- We couldn't do that before. - Right.
- So... - Look at the back.
Please read the poem written by Park Gap Sun.
Tears welled up in my eyes.
Right.
- Park Gap Sun wrote it. - Yes.
("My First Test")
"I took my first test."
"I should've taken some calming pills."
"I didn't know anything when I got married,"
"when I said my final goodbye to my husband,"
"and when my five children got married."
"I didn't know my heart could pound like this."
"I'm in a new world now."
"I have new friends. My teachers adore me."
"Every day is filled with happiness."
She wrote a poem about her first test.
You read the poem so fluently,
so it's easy to understand.
You liked it because I read it smoothly.
You read it properly.
- The Meokgol Station is here. - Yes.
Have you lived around here for a long time?
I live in Hagye-dong.
I used to live in Gongneung-dong.
What?
Where in Gongneung-dong?
- Pardon? - Where in Gongneung-dong?
So I went to Gongneung Elementary School.
In that case,
you must've gone to school with my daughter.
How old is your daughter?
She's married. She's all grown up.
Right? I mean, she went to that school.
- Did I... - He's married too.
- I didn't ask for a blind date. - To Gongneung Elementary School.
- Jae Seok is... - Wait a second.
- What are you talking about? - Suddenly...
Suddenly, she puts up a wall.
Come on. Ho Yeon. Jung Min.
I didn't ask you to set me up with her.
- Gosh. - My goodness.
(My daughter is the best.)
Now, we want...
- to give you presents. - We have to play a game.
We'll give you presents by playing a game.
It's Round One.
Okay. Round One.
"Onnuri Gift Certificate."
- What does it say? - It's 300 dollars.
It's a 300-dollar...
- Onnuri Gift Certificate. - It's 300 dollars.
No.
- It's a 300-dollar gift voucher. - That's not enough.
- But... - It's for Round One.
That's right.
Okay. What's for Round One?
(Chalk Alkkagi)
(They will flick a bottle cap...)
(to knock down chalk.)
(Round 1: Knock down 2 chalks.)
- What? It's Alkkagi. - It's Alkkagi.
- Chalk Alkkagi? - Bottle Cap Alkkagi?
Jung Min said he was good at it.
(Just a moment ago, in the cab...)
I'm really good at Alkkagi.
- Are you good at it? - Yes.
You played it once on a go board.
- We did. - Yes.
When you flicked the stone, it popped up.
I went, "Gosh. they should change the angle."
You have to use your thumb. When you flick it with your thumb,
it will go straight and hit the stone.
"Gosh. They don't know the trick."
(He was so loud about it.)
(Now, it's time to prove himself.)
- Jung Min. - It's Jung Min's specialty.
- Gosh. - He said he was confident.
- Your time has come. - It's here.
Now that I need to play it...
after bragging about it,
I shouldn't suck at it.
He said Alkkagi was his game.
Jung Min, the opportunity is here.
Here's your chance. Either you'll be a hero or...
Be careful what you wish for.
(Getting into the posture)
(How good will the self-proclaimed Alkkagi master be?)
- Hold on. - What?
(Retrieving it in a hurry)
- What was that? - Don't be nervous.
Jung Min, don't fool around.
Gosh. It's actually...
Something is wrong.
The game you're the most confident about.
It won't work.
(His skills are quickly exposed.)
(Their high expectations drop at once.)
- It's so far. - You can practice together.
- They're far away. - What? Ho Yeon.
(The cap barely misses it.)
Nice and powerful.
(The real master has emerged.)
(Aiming carefully)
(Right on the target)
You shattered it.
- Gosh. Nice. - It's a success.
- I... - Ho Yeon.
Ho Yeon, you're on fire today.
Ho Yeon is better than Jung Min.
- Exactly. - Let's go for Round One.
- Shall we? - Yes.
We'll try our best.
Okay. One, two, three.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Okay. We have 20 seconds. - We have 20 seconds.
- I'll go 1st. - You'll go 1st.
- I'll try going 1st. - I'll go 2nd.
I'll go second because you're good.
Did you say I was good?
- I'll go third, Jae Seok. - Yes, Ho Yeon.
I'll go fourth. Okay.
I have a feeling it'll be done before I try.
- I'll end it. - Okay.
- Hold on. - Go, Yeon Seok.
Hold on.
We should succeed at it easily as it's Round One.
(Placing it carefully)
Where is the tripod?
- It's back there. - He's going to try it.
- We need to clap for him. - Go, Yeon Seok.
(Whispering)
Get it.
Get it in one go.
(He was about to try it,)
(but he stops.)
(Overwhelmed with pressure)
Get it in one go.
(Praying devoutly for him to succeed)
I don't know if I'll get it in one go,
but here I go!
- There he goes. - Go.
First try. Ready.
Set...
(We have to make it happen in this spare time.)
(1st try, Yeon Seok)
Gosh. Why? It was too strong.
(It was too strong.)
(1st try, Jung Min)
(Self-proclaimed master of Alkkagi goes for it.)
Okay. Ho Yeon.
Keep the time in mind.
- In 5, 4... - We have 5 seconds.
Place it next to you.
- Two, one. - This will count.
(He flicked it with 1 second left.)
This will count.
(Will they pass Round 1 at once?)
(1st try, Jae Seok)
- Darn it. - Goodness.
- It missed the mark. - It's too slippery.
(First try failed)
(Comforting them with laughter)
(Booing)
(Her true feelings came out)
It's...
- She booed. - You didn't boo us, did you?
(You didn't boo us, did you?)
(Embarrassed)
Now, we'll move on right away.
I'll try it right away.
This is our 2nd try. Now, 1, 2, 3.
- Here we go. - Here I go.
Let's nail it this time.
Ready.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 2.)
Set...
(2nd try, Jae Seok)
- That's it. - Hold on.
(Off to a good start)
(2nd try, Ho Yeon)
- Darn it. - Gosh.
Go, Jung Min.
(2nd try, Jung Min)
Darn it.
Okay. Five, four,
- We have time. - three,
two, one.
(2nd try, Yeon Seok)
I knew you'd do it, Yeon Seok.
One.
(It's a buzzer beater for Yeon Seok.)
(They had a dramatic win.)
Okay.
(Thrilled)
Okay. Round One,
- success. - Success.
(Round 1, success)
Ma'am.
(Jae Seok and Yeon Seok nailed it.)
Ma'am, you won 300 dollars.
(From Round 1, they've secured a 300-dollar gift certificate.)
(Screaming)
Now, it's time to decide...
if you want to move on to Round Two. Go or stop?
We still have eight tries left.
Go?
- Go for it. - Go?
She wants us to go for it.
- "Go for it." - "Go for it." It's a go.
- "Go for it." - Now, it's Round Two.
- Round One ended quickly. - Yes.
So you have to go for Round Two.
They can stop if they want.
It's the same one.
- Onnuri Gift Certificate. - Onnuri Gift Certificate.
- It's 500 dollars. - It's 500 dollars.
- A 500-dollar gift certificate. - It's Onnuri Gift Certificate.
(Delighted)
(Surprised)
- You have gift certificates... - Gosh.
- Then... - that are worth 800 dollars.
It's 800 dollars total.
(A total of 800 dollars)
You look happy.
- Please do your best. - Yes.
- Goodness. - Do your best.
(Round 2)
(Knock down 3 chalks.)
- We have three chalks now. - But this is...
When we get the middle one, the rest are wide open.
- Yes. - It won't be easy, will it?
Just think that it'd be the same as the last round.
- Let's go for it. - Let's try it.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Go! - Go!
I'll go first. Okay.
Go, Jung Min.
- Say, "Here I go." - Here I go.
- Here we go. - Ready.
Set...
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 3.)
(3rd try, Jung Min)
- That was nice. - Goodness.
(3rd try, Jae Seok)
Aim for the edge.
Is that an obstacle now?
(3rd try, Jae Seok)
(Jae Seok knocks it down too.)
What? Wait.
(3rd try, Yeon Seok)
We have time.
You have five seconds.
- Four, three, - Gosh.
Ho Yeon.
- two, one. - Take your time.
(Take your time.)
One.
(3rd try, Ho Yeon)
That was close. What a shame.
It's okay.
(Failed)
(Reading the room)
(Nodding)
Gosh. You two nailed it consecutively.
That was good, though.
Now, we still...
My heart is racing.
- It's fun, isn't it? - I was afraid you'd miss it.
Right.
- Now, it's our fourth try, right? - Yes.
Do you want to go first?
- Should I go 1st? - Okay. Go 1st.
- Go 1st. - You go 1st.
Do you want to go last?
- Okay, you go last. - Okay.
- Go, Ho Yeon. - Let's go.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 4.)
- Here we go. - Here we go.
- Ready. - It's 20 seconds, right?
Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 4.)
(4th try, Ho Yeon)
Goodness.
- Okay. - I have a headache.
(4th try, Yeon Seok)
- Nice. - Goodness.
I did it.
(4th try, Jae Seok)
(Another chance has arisen.)
(4th try, Jung Min)
- Five, - We don't have time.
(5 seconds left)
- four, three, - We have time, Jung Min.
We have enough time.
(4th try, Jung Min)
two, one.
(Roar of victory!)
We did it.
You won 800 dollars!
(It's time to celebrate!)
(Touched)
(Round 2, success)
Okay. We did it.
Mom, you won 800 dollars.
(They've secured gift certificates of 300 dollars and 800 dollars.)
- Now, stop. - Ma'am, stop.
It's 200 dollars for each, which is perfect.
- Or is it wrong? - It's wrong. It's 800 dollars.
Then, you get 200 dollars each, and I get 200 dollars too.
No. You can't do that.
Now...
We've succeeded in our fourth try, which is fast.
Also, we haven't used the chance.
- We still have one chance. - Don't listen to them.
They're evil snakes.
We lost our last game this way,
so the guests left empty-handed.
So, just end the game here, ma'am.
- Ma'am. - Okay.
- Do you want to try one more time? - What should we do?
We have six tries and a chance left.
But the game will get tougher.
- If we fail, - We won't have any presents.
- your presents will be gone. - They'll be gone.
Please discuss it carefully.
We won't look, so think about it.
You should listen to me.
During the last game we had,
we blew it all.
Just take 800 dollars.
Whatever. We'll go for it.
Come on. They're evil snakes.
- Now... - Seriously.
- Okay. Ye Sun will pick. - Let me see.
(What is the present for Round 3?)
We'll read it together.
- "It's too hot..." - "It's too hot..."
- "to study..." - "to study..."
- "in the middle of summer." - "in the middle of summer."
- "Samsung's..." - Okay.
- "floor-standing..." - "Floor-standing."
- "AC?" - "AC."
(Round 3 present: Samsung floor-standing AC)
It's a Samsung floor-standing AC.
Samsung has appeared...
- like an advertisement. - Really.
(Overflowed with happiness)
(Stomping with joy)
Actually, unlike the other parts,
they read "Samsung" very clearly.
(They articulated the big brand's name.)
They articulated it.
- Darn. - So, what's the mission?
(Round 3)
(Knock down 5 chalks...)
(in 30 seconds.)
(But the one who succeeds may continue to flick the cap.)
We can keep flicking.
The one who succeeded can flick as many stones.
- I see. - In that case...
Once we knock one chalk, we can keep going.
(Practicing right away)
Without that rule, we can't get the fifth one.
- That's it. - You get another try, then.
Another cap.
If you miss it, your turn is passed.
- In this case, - Now,
- we move on. - to the next person.
(If one fails, the next one tries.)
He can flick again now.
(He can keep going like this.)
He's perfect.
- It's a success. - Nice.
- Okay. - Okay.
- I got it. - Go for it.
- Let's do it. - Yes. We have a chance.
(Taking off her leather jacket to play)
Let's cheer up.
Finally, she took off her jacket.
"Finally."
Let's go!
- Let's do it together. - Since we've reached Round Three.
It's Round Three. Let's get the air conditioner.
- One, two, three! Let's go! - Let's go!
All right.
- Here we go! - Ready.
Set...
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 5.)
- We have to give them presents. - Right.
- I think she can do it! - Gosh.
- Do I go second? It's me? - Yes.
(5th try, Ho Yeon)
- Nice one! - Gosh!
You did well.
- You did it, Jae Seok! - Gosh!
What? I think he'll make it.
- I think he'll make it. - Gosh!
(He hits 3 consecutively.)
- There are two left. - End it!
End it!
(5th try, Jae Seok)
Just hit two.
One each.
(There are 2 chalks left.)
Let's do this.
Ten seconds left.
- Gosh! - Jung Min.
They're left at the toughest spots. My gosh.
Oh, no!
- Five, four, three, - Nice!
- Please! - two, one.
(Please hit one more!)
One.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
It brushed past it!
One.
(The chalk shakes.)
It brushed past it! Gosh!
It brushed past it!
- Gosh! - Gosh!
Gosh, that was so close!
(Jae Seok's 3 consecutive shots end with a bad result.)
We have four tries left.
- "Five, four, three..." - You can use the chance any time.
- "Five, four, three, two, one." - There are four tries left.
- That drives you crazy. - That drives you crazy.
Say it quietly.
"Five, four!" Not like this.
"Five, four..." Got it?
- Gosh, that was so close. - Gosh, that stressed me out.
You may use the chance whenever you wish to.
We have four tries left.
- Should we use the chance? - Should we do that?
- The chance? - Let's use the chance.
- The chance. - Right.
(Chance)
Pick 1 out of these 5.
Which one shall I pick?
(A good chance is needed to change the mood.)
That one.
- All right. - It should be a good one.
What is it?
"Lucky. The ace takes on this try alone."
I knew it. The chances won't help.
This is the same one as earlier.
(It's a good chance, but they have a bad memory about it.)
This isn't a very good chance.
- You should do it. - Jae Seok should do it alone.
Jae Seok is the best one out of us.
- Then, Jae Seok should do it. - Right.
- He'll be our ace. - Right. Let's do this.
- He's doing well right now. - Right.
- You have four lives. - Right. I know.
(Jae Seok will take the role of all 4.)
Should I go for it right away?
- Go for it. - Right.
I think it'll be okay. I'll place them down for you.
All right. Here I go!
- Here we go! - Ready.
- Set. - Let's go!
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 7.)
(He fails with his 1st shot.)
(He fails with his 2nd shot.)
(Jae Seok?)
- Gosh! - What's wrong?
(He's already left with only one life.)
You did it! Nice!
(He fails if he misses this shot.)
(Shaking)
(7th try, one life left)
You did it! Nice!
Is that not allowed?
Nice.
- Nice! - You're still alive.
- I'm still alive. - You're still alive.
(It isn't over until it's over.)
(7th try, one life left)
- Ten seconds left. - Gosh!
Gosh!
(They fail with the seventh try even after using the chance.)
Gosh. It's okay.
(His eyes change.)
He did so well earlier.
How did he throw away three lives so easily like that?
My gosh!
- Gosh, my nose is runny. - Things aren't working out today.
- Things aren't going our way. - Right.
- As I kept taking the shots... - It hurts, doesn't it?
- Gosh. - It must hurt.
- There are no more now. - We shouldn't have used the chance!
- There are no more now. - I shouldn't have listened to him!
Gosh!
- But... - See?
She's starting to curse now!
- Gosh, why did you do that? - Gosh.
She's starting to reveal her true character now.
All right.
- It's our 9th try. We have 2 left. - It's the 9th try.
- We must make it this time. - We must make it this time.
- Ho Yeon! - Yes?
- You're ready, right? - Yes.
- Here I go! - Here I go!
Ready. Set...
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 9.)
Gosh!
(9th try, Jae Seok)
(Two of them fail right away.)
- Gosh! - Gosh!
What are you guys doing? Gosh!
(9th try, Jung Min)
Gosh!
Let's go!
- Yes! - Nice!
(He knocks down two quickly.)
(9th try, Jung Min)
- Ten seconds left! - Nice!
(What?)
(9th try, Jung Min)
- Gosh! - Gosh!
(Ninth try failed)
(Speechless)
What are you guys doing?
(Ashamed)
Good job!
- I'll show you, Ho Yeon. - Right.
- You placed it here, right? - Yes.
- It kept going there, right? - Yes.
- Don't look at the chalk. - Okay.
This is where you have to look. Look over here.
Try to hit this part.
- That part? - Yes.
Take your shot while aiming for that part.
See?
What was that?
You get what I'm saying, right?
- Try again. - Try again.
(They try the off-aim strategy once again.)
It's right here.
Try to hit this part.
- Nice. You did it. - See?
You got it, right?
Just do that.
(A perfect private lesson for Ho Yeon)
- Got it? - Yes.
- You'll be able to hit one. - Right.
- We have to really focus. - This is exciting.
The previous try was...
All right!
(They're down to their tenth try.)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- We'll do our best! - We'll do our best!
- One, two, three! Let's go! - One, two, three! Let's go!
(One last cheer)
- Go! - Go!
- Let's go! - Where did I tell you to look?
- There. All right. - Right. You got it, right?
All right.
- Here I go! - Ready.
You can do it!
- "I can do it!" - You can do it! "I can do it!"
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on the last try.)
- "I can do it!" - Nice!
That's two!
- Nice! - That's two!
- Two in one go! - That was nice.
Do the exact same thing.
(Last try, Ho Yeon)
- You're second. - Good job.
You can do it!
(Last try, Jae Seok)
- You can do it! - Gosh.
You can do it!
(Last try, Yeon Seok)
That doesn't count?
(Last try, Jung Min)
Ten seconds left.
- Let's go! - You can do it!
Let's go.
(The last player has 2 chalks left.)
You can do it!
- You can do it! - There are two left.
(Last try, Jung Min)
(It's over.)
- You can do it! - There are two left.
(They fail with 2 left.)
It's over!
- Hold on. - Gosh!
Hold on.
Gosh.
- Why did I... - Gosh.
(The place of learning turns silent.)
One more chance!
- One more chance! - One more chance!
- One more chance! - We could get...
another ace chance.
You've already used it once.
- Hold on. We should... - Gosh.
Well...
How disappointing!
- We're sorry. - It's disappointing.
(They can't hide their disappointment.)
A game is a game. There's nothing we can do.
- All right. These are... - Gosh, this is so disappointing.
from us.
Take one each. These are our merch.
Right. Thank you!
- We're sorry. - We're sorry.
- We're so sorry. - Gosh.
They're all leaving.
- Please! - Gosh.
- I want to cry. - Gosh!
(The ladies slowly disappear.)
- Gosh. - How was it today?
- Right. - How was it today?
- We must ask about today. - What?
Jung Min and Ho Yeon joined us today.
You two went through so much.
It was a disappointing way to end the day.
How was it today?
(They started with "Hope" but failed twice at Round 3.)
(Struggling to move on)
(He expresses his feelings through the table tennis ball.)
- How would I feel right now? - Out of regret,
he took out the table tennis ball from his pocket. Gosh.
My heart feels heavy...
as we have to leave without achieving anything.
How can we meet our members after this?
- Well... - They'll ask, "How did it go?"
We'll have to say, "We failed."
(The representatives of "Hope" faced a bitter end.)
- Please come again... - Right.
and give us a chance to redeem ourselves.
- We'll do better next time. - Right.
(The dopamine missed from today will be found through "Hope.")
(Guests on a hot summer day)
(Definition of romance, Jung Hae In)
(Definition of film noir, Heo Sung Tae)
(The encounter of the opposites)
(Hae In is like the main character of a romance comic.)
(No way!)
(What is it?)
(Actual footage of Jung Hae In complaining in an ugly way)
(Hae In gets angry as well.)
(Feeling dizzy)
(He gets angry...)
(and sweats buckets.)
(Sung Tae with super villain looks)
(Gosh, that hurts.)
(He keeps acting like a fool.)
(Did you get a brain freeze after eating the bingsu?)
(Sung Tae is weak in many different ways.)
(These two are unpredictable.)
(They spend a hot day together...)
(that is hotter than any other day.)
(Whenever Possible Season 5)